BRYANT MACMAHON

FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Full Stack Software Engineer with 5+ years of experience in Business Management. Problem solving enthusiast and strong communicator with fervor to bring skills, talents and energy to a development team solving innovative and challenging software issues.

SKILLS

Coding Languages

Javascript, Python, CSS, HTML, SQL, Ruby

Frameworks/Technologies

Flask, Node.js, Express, React, Redux, jQuery, Jest, Jasmine, Vue, Lodash, REST APIs, Rails, Bootstrap, Chrome Devtools, Bash/Shell, Visual Studio, Bootstrap, Markdown, Git

Key Strengths

Googling, Test Driven Development, Agile

EDUCATION

Springboard Software Engineering Career Track | March 2021 - January 2022

- Mastering skills in front-end web development, back-end web development, databases, data structures and algorithms.
- Weekly 1 on 1 meetings with a senior level, industry expert.
- 700+ hours of course material
- 200+ hours of coding immersion

Indiana University - School of Public and Environmental Affairs | September 2011 - June 2013

- Treasurer, Inter-fraternity Council
- Social Chair, Theta Chi Fraternity

EXPERIENCE

Front End Web Developer

Bird Digital | December 2020 - April 2021

- Designed and deployed static websites for customers from varying industries.
- Managed entire project process from sale to deployment.

Store Manager

T-Mobile | July 2020 - December 2020

- Oversaw all aspects of the sales floor including scheduling, escalations, inventory, employee training, financial discrepancies and problem solving.
- Consistently exceeded monthly overall sales and specific revenue stream goals.
- Troubleshot extensive carrier and crippling device issues with customers.

Assistant Manager

Brother's Bar and Grill | Dec 2016 - June 2020

- Guided sales initiatives to optimize month over month financial growth.
- Conducted job interviews, evaluated employees skills, and mentored new hires into becoming successful team members.

CONTACT

Main Cell: 208-908-3163 Work Cell: 503-421-0374 Email: bryantmac@gmail.com Portfolio: https://zataara.xyz Location: Portland, OR 97232

LinkedIn: @bryantmac Github: @zataara